<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NGO</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="thank_you_for_donation">Thank you for your Donation Our Team will Contact you Shortly</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="activities_text">\nHelping Mentally, Physically, Financially troubled people, Spreading Awareness, Providing Education and Donation to the needful, Organizing Spiritual trips
    </string>
    <string name="summary_text">We are a non-profit organization, Udaghosh Social Welfare Society registered in 2014 is based in Bhopal (M.P.)
        India. We hope for a discrimination-free future and act towards making that a reality where people dont have to
        fight for their basic necessities, rights, and security. We focus on enabling equal access to quality education,
        healthcare, shelter, clothes, food, and water for all. Udaghosh Social Welfare Society works with the most vulnerable
        and marginalized members of our society to ensure they get the opportunities they deserve to improve their lives as well
        as their future generation. We also focus on girls and women to ensure they live in a violence-free environment with the
        freedom to expand their minds.</string>
    <string name="long_term_impact_text">This Empowerment Project prepares girls to meet the challenges of their generation by giving them tools, awareness and knowledge to avoid negative outcomes for self-sufficiency, educational attainment, life enhancement and ultimate success.</string>
    <string name="need_text">Historically at-risk and traditionally underserved,  girls of African descent are disproportionately affected by poverty, teen pregnancy, school dropout, HIV/AIDS and other sexually transmitted diseases (STD’s). Due to demand, Sisterhood Agenda and partner organizations implement A Journey Toward Womanhood on-site at different locations and provide much-needed training and educational resources such as curriculum guides, student manuals, program protocols, books, knowledge cards, and journals.</string>
</resources>